Sometimes it feels wrong to do good to my witch sister.
Suddenly today
a beggar comes in front of my car.  Hey, this is
my sister.  So today is 15th August and I can
never be free from my family,
so I am taking them to my grandmother's
house.  But then on the way my secret gets revealed
and to keep him quiet in front of mom,
I
fed him ice cream as a bribe.  Then we directly reached grandmother's
house and their conversation was going on there.
But I tied my ears and went to the
terrace to fly a kite and I was just thinking
that Riya might come.  But when you mention the name of Satan,
Satan appears.  And madam ji was adamant
that I wanted to fly a kite.  And then this madam
hugged me after getting her hand cut.  So now
I assigned her a new task and went downstairs and
mom [ __ ] me.  And now tell me
what is my fault in this?   The
rest of you are making a big mistake.
I posted a nice little vlog.
Click on the link below to go